nanacast.com 2016-06-09

# Privacy Policy

Nanacast.com PRIVACY POLICY

Internet Business Ideas Inc. and Nanacast.com strive to offer visitors the many advantages of Internet technology and to provide an interactive and personalized experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any unauthorized third party. Period.

How we gather information from users

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to the services provided on our site or when you request access to certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you purchase products, participate in message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site. Like most Web sites, Nanacast.com and Internet Business Ideas Inc. also collect information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, we use cookie and ip address tracking to customize and improve your experience on our site.

What we do with the information we collect

Our system may place and track cookies as well as log your IP address. If you purchase, or obtain for free, products and services from Nanacast.com and Internet BUsiness ideas Inc. our system we will collect and record the information necessary to process billing related transactions whether they be one time or recurring subscriptions. We also may collect information such as email addresses to facilitate the creation of secure private accounts to allow you to access products and services as well as email subscriptions and newsletters. We may also collect data such as Federal Tax ID numbers for tax reporting purposes from US residents who participate in our affiliate program.

If you join Nanacast.com for the purpose of becoming an affiliate in the Nanacast.com affiliate network and if you apply or join the affiliate programs of third party publishers besides Internet Business Ideas Inc. we will share with those publisher's who's affiliate programs you are joined to all information necessary for them to contact you and provide you with affiliate commission payments via paypal or check.

If you are using the Nanacast.com ecommerce system to purchase products and services from third party publishers we will collect all information required to process your order as well as any recurring subscriptions associated with your order if any. This information will be shared directly with the publisher whom you are making the purchase from or entering into a subscription with.

At no time will your personal information be rented, sold, or shared with any unathorized third party. You specifically authorize Internet Business ideas Inc. to share applicable personal, billing, affiliate, and membership account information such as your name, company name, website, and phone number with any third party company who's affiliate program you are joined to or which you join in the future through the Nanacast.com system, and any third party company whom you purchase products, services, and/or subscriptions from.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services as well as the products and services of third party publishers using Nanacast.com (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on Nanacast.com or by Internet Business Ideas Inc. to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; your customer account, products purchases and subscriptions, your publisher account, your affiliate account or about our Terms of Service and privacy policy; as well as services and products offered by Internet Business Ideas Inc. Nanacast.com and third party publishers using the Nanacast.com system and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by Internet Business Ideas Inc. and Nanacast.com may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge, partner, or joint venture with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements

Internet Business Ideas Inc. and Nanacast.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including Nanacast.com publishers, partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a Internet Business Ideas Inc. or Nanacast.com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through Internet Business Ideas Inc. and Nanacast.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. Internet Business Ideas Inc. is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our publishers, advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before or were referred to their site while visiting one of our websites. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. Internet Business Ideas Inc. does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Internet Business Ideas Inc. and Nanacast.com and this policy.

Children

You must be Eighteen (18) Years of age or older to access this website. If you are under eighteen years of age, you are not authorized to access this website for any reason.

Internet Business Ideas Inc. does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe Internet Business Ideas Inc. and Nanacast.com has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us at the address listed below.

Contacting Us.

We can be reached by contacting:

Internet Business Ideas Inc.

1900 grassmere Street Boise, ID 83709

Changes to this Policy

Internet Business Ideas Inc. reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

SEVERABILITY.

If any provision of this Agreement shall be held to be invalid or unenforceable for any reason, the remaining provisions shall continue to be valid and enforceable. If a court finds that any provision of this Agreement is invalid or unenforceable, but that by limiting such provision it would become valid or enforceable, then such provision shall be deemed to be written, construed, and enforced as so limited.

WAIVER OF CONTRACTUAL RIGHT.

The failure of Nanacast.com and Internet Business Ideas Inc. to enforce any provision of this Agreement shall not be construed as a waiver or limitation of that party’s right to subsequently enforce and compel strict compliance with every provision of this Agreement.

APPLICABLE LAW JURISDICTION AND VENU

This Agreement in all respects shall be governed by and construed according to the laws of the State of Idaho, to the exclusion of any other applicable body of governing law, without regard to conflicts of laws principles. This Agreement is entered into in Ada County, Idaho. You consent to the exclusive jurisdiction of Idaho for any dispute arising from or related to this agreement. You agree that the exclusive venue for any dispute arising from or related to this Agreement will be a court located in Ada County, Idaho.
